Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2020; 1965-ongoing RL.00617
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Latin American and Caribbean Programs, 1987-2010; 30 boxes
  - Bolivia 98-99 DFID Year 2 + INOPAL FY 98 working files: Trip reports 98-99, evaluation/complications; reports/sites MOH; new ideas 98; dissemination mtg 98; comms 98-99; reports 98-99; DFID proposal 99; DFID project development 99; info policy 99; USAID presentation 99; Pathfinder 99; matrix lessons 99; project planning 99; office 99; Allison diagnostics 99; responsibility charting 00; INOPAL reports 99; S Rance work DFID 99; production registration 99; PRIME presentation 99; inventory La Paz 99; country team 99; Frontiers 99; DMPA study 99; PRIME working files 99: background, proposal/workplan, Bolivia office, comms PRIME, comms USAID, comms other, trip reports, monthly reports, reports – general project, eval/monitoring, dissemination/articles; Bol LAC donor report 99; LAC mtg 99; logbook info 99; literature/background 99 -00; general Bolivia program 99-00 (Box 148)
  - Bolivia 2000-2001 LAC strategic planning – country plans 00; PAC training report La Pax & Santa Cruz 00; logframe 00; training course reports DFID 00; Frontiers informe preliminary 00; background info 00; convenio Santa Cruz 00; monthly reports 00; LAC strategic plan update 00; monitoring instruments 00; LAC presentation 00; DFID 2 proposal 00; palmtop forms M&E 00; M&E senior staff 00; DFID proposal prep 00; PRIME PI 00; Kenya scaling up mtg 00; program effort & Index 00; site evals 00; HR&D 00; workplan 00; gender articles 00; informes 00; marketing/communication 00; logframe 00; articles 00; project progress grids 00; TSDI management 00; Ipas marketing 00; PRIME PAC breakout session 00; M&E 00; TSDI mtg notes 00; PAC courses Santa Cruz 00; PAC workshop program 00; project memorandum 00; gender task force 00-01; Men and abortion 01 (Box 149)
  - Bolivia and Miscellaneous Contries 00-10: Standards/Guidelines 00; Talleres de APA 01; In-country Donor Docs 03-04; Uruguay Workshop Rpt 8-04; FY05; SV Protocols 05; Bolivia Correspondences FY05; Policy/Research – Bolivia FY05; MSI-Ipas SV Project 05; Donor Reports/Proposals-FY 05; Bolivia Program Review 05; UNFPA-Bolivia SV Project 05; Memoria 2005-2008; Bolivia Communications 05-08; Bolivia office move/contracts 06; Plan I'natl 06; Sub-regional ToT July 2005 FY06; CE Mtg/Plan UK 06; Bolivia Policy SRR 06-08; Printed Materials: DFID/MSI Project 06-08; DFID/MSI 07; SV/AB Conf proceedings 07; Bolivia Country Plans 07-09; SV Project – Mid-term eval FY08; Policy 09-10; Country Office FY10; Miso FY10; SVRI FY10 Misc. Countries 01-10: Argentina 04-05; Argentina 2005; Argentina FY06; Argentina Pubs 07; AR FAMG 10; Caribbean 05-06; Cuba 06; Colombia EC 01; COL Women's Link 06; Colombia 07; Col La Mesa FY07; Paraguay 03; Paraguay FY06; Peru SV study proposal 04; Peru FY 05; Peru FY06; CLACAI Full Mtg. Report 06; Peru Legal Ab Care Protocol 07; Peru PROMSEX Contract 09; Uruguay FY05; Uruguay 05; Uruguay HC guidelines FY06 (Box 184)
  - Brazil, Mexico, Central America 89-10: Brazil 02-10: Research – Medical Opinions – Rape Victims 02; CFEMEA Summary 03; SV Seminar Report 04; LA mtg 04; Standards & Guidelines 04-05; Donor Proposals 04-05; Donor Reports/Proposals FY05; Pará State Protocol: SV Victimes 06; PPD 06; Donor Docs FY 06-07; Market Analysis MVA 07; Aborto Induzido Opinião 07; Santa Clara/SV Campaign 07; Conscientious objection/human rights FY07; Ipas letters FY08; Report on Policy work 08; SRR/Human Rights 09; Anti-choice scan 09; Donor Report 10; Brazil MVA Registration FY10 Mexico 89-10: Mex DF AB proposal study 89; Michoacan 94; T&L 00-03; General Background 00-04; M&E 01-03; Country Plan 01-04; Mexico-Abortion Law 01-06; Country Summary 02; Donor Proposal 02; Miso hemorrhage Thesis in Mex 02; Mexico Objectives 02-05; Mexico Program Review 02-5; Mexico Trip Reports 02-05; Planning 03; Ipas Mex SV pubs 03; Donor Reports & Proposals 03; Donor Proposals & Reports 04; Publications/Mats – Mexico FY05; Policy/Research Mexico FY05; Donor reports/Proposals – Mexico FY05; L.A. project 05; Ipas Exec Visit 05; Pro-Choice Alliance Report FY06; Donor Proposals and Reports FY06; Office Lease FY06; Mexico Lease 2006; Mexico Donor proposal/reports 06-07; Donor Proposals & Reports 07; ANON 2 – Alianza 07; Comms 07; Abortion Guidelines DF 07; Adolescents Projects 07-08; Program Plan 07-09; Donor Proposals & Reports FY08; Todas 08; OE Proposal 08; Legal Issues 09; Alianza planning mtg 09; Program Data 09; Alianza/Ipas Analysis 09; Clinical Affairs FY09; AdvocacyWork plan 09-10; WCG FY10; Advocacy FY10; Presentations FY10 Central America 01-10: Nica PAC training module 01; Donor Report 02; Ipas CA Update 02; Panama 03; Policy/Research – Central America FY05; El Salvador Nat'l RH plan 05; Donor Report SAF Access 05; Legal strategies meeting FY06; El Salvador 06; Consortium – Therapeutic Ab. 07; NICA CEDAW Materials 07; Donor Docs 07; Therapeutic Ab Legal 07; Rosa Case Analysis 07; Carmen Climaco & NYT 07; Comms 07; Contract MINSA 08; Gomez contract 08; Nica – therapeutic AB group proposal 09; Nica MOH MM Presentation 09; Planning 09; Nica Advocacy Donor Report 10; Bolivia Legal Reform FY10 (Box 182)
  - Brazil: trip reports; project development; donor documents; contracts; reports; correspondence; Jabaquara; CRSMNADI; CEPIA; Adesse; da Mota; MEAC; Pathfinder; Cesar Cals; Chizuro; UFRJ Maternidade; SOS Corp; ECOS; Jabaquara working files; legal abortion program; BART files; communications; donor report; MVA cost/benefit report, 1989-1996 (Box 27)
  - Brazil: working files from all years (proposals, reports, database, conferences, equipment; activity reports, correspondence, etc.), 1997-2001 (Box 28)
  - NICA: Si Mujer; Tipitapa, DeProsse eval; Jarquin; hospital reports; MINSA; Work Bank evaluation; working files; correspondence; country plan; country team; general file, 1985-2002 (Box 29)
  - LAC: Mexico 82-06: PAC 06; OB/GYN congress 06; Alliance report 05-06; program planning 04; Gire 03; program binder 02; MVA sales/OBgyn congress 97; MVA training 97; workshops 97-04; IMSS Solidaridad 97 working files; donor reports 02-06; donor reports/proposals 97-98; proposals/reports 97; donor comms 97; consultants 97; marketing project 97; comms 97; Morelos midwives training 97; Safe Motherhood mtg 97; product registration 97; monthly updates 97-97; research projects 96-97; Oaxaca PAC training/eval 96; office ops 96; Andrea Saldana reports 96; marketing projects 95-97; Mexico office registration 95; natl pop plan 95; MVA studies 95-95; Zacatecas PAC study results 92; Sonoroa/Sinaloa working files 89-92; MCH training 88; Monterrey clinic 82; El Oro project 86-87 (Box 124)
  - LAC region: Bolivia/Brazil/Monitoring: Bolivia 00-06: Bolivia office 05-06; MOH Norms; donor reports/proposals 06; consultant reports/sexual violence 03-04; partner agreements 02; donor reports/proposals 02-04; program binder 02; eval of hospital services 00; PAC 95-06; Coms 92-05; PAC study 01:Brazil 00-06: sexual violence; comms; legal reform 06; donor reports/proposals 06; lit review 05; AMPARO 04; Follow-up on complications 04; reports/studies 02-03; program binder 02; donor reports 01-06; operations 01-02; strategic plan 00-04; marketing 00-05; LAC region Monitoring notebook: 04-05 (Box 125)
  - LAC Region: Venezuela: 86-87 Uruguay: PAC training report 05; reform 03-04: Peru: legal 04-05; training course 01-02; training numbers 02; program binder 02; study tour comms 01-02; reports 01-02; Ayacucho PAC 01; reports/conferences/mtgs 00-01; eval Condo Grande project 02; donor proposals 01; program planning 01; development 01-01; country plan 00-01; country team marketing 00; partners/agreements/mtgs 00-01; corresp 00; office ops 00-03: Paraguay: background; Nicaragua: program binder 02; donor reports/proposals 01-06; corres MMB; La Campana 28 de September 04-07; ICCO project eval 06; ICCO contract 02; Rosa case 03; proposals 03; fundraising 01; ops 01-03; Ob/Gyn mtg report 01; Honduras: MVA training 88; El Salvador: MM study 06; Guyana: background 01-02; corresp 99-03; media clippings 99-01; Ecuador: coms/trip report 02-04; MOH agreement 02; donor report hospital training program 86-89; working file hospital training program 86-89; Colombia: legal reform women's Link contract 06; AVSC project 96-97 (Box 126)
  - LAC region: Internal training 06; EC 06; small grants 06; strat planning 06; donor reports/proposals 05-06; med abortion 05; SV report 05; donor reports/proposals 03; key partners FLASOG/FIGO 05; GTN 04; org planning 04; WHO strategic committee 05; SV comms 03-04; SV 02-04; SV background; country summaries 03; M&E 02; newsletter 02; development comms 02-04; program review 02; UNFPA SV donor; reports/proposals 01-04; advocacy comms 01-04; MVA training sales 01-04; donor reports/proposals 01-02; impt comms 01-03; MVA training numbers 01; regional management 01; program activities reports 00-01; strat plans 00-04; regional update 00; presentations 99-02; regional summary 99-04; strat planning 99; strat planning 98-04; conferences 97-04; marketing 96-97; trip reports 96-06; LAC PAC (LART) 95-99; conferences 86-87 (Box 127)
  - Latin America Regional 01-10: SV Proposals/RM Chat 01-04; Health Care workers proposal 02; BAC Staff Advisory Group 02; Development 02; Sexual Violence Background 03; Program Reviews FY03; MVA Lessons Learned 04; Women's Health policies conf 04; UN-SV Proposal 04; MA Best Practices Mtg 04; Region Management 04-05; Directors Survey 05; Donor Proposal/Reports FY06; TSDI/PP&D – LAC Region FY 05; MA 05; R&E/Policy/Communications – LAC Region FY 05; Catholics for Choice 05; FLASOG sexual violence workshop FY05; Sexual Violence background 05; SV Background 05; Intercambios 05; Donor Proposals/Reports FY05; Articles-Lit Review SV 05; UNFPA SV Project FY05-06; TSDI/PP&D LAC Region FY 06; List of SV pubs 06; Regional Donor Report FY06; Intercambios Contract FY06; Womens Link Worldwide 06; GEM FY06; SAAF (RFP, etc.) 06; Board/Donor Visit Mats 06-07; MedSchools Project FY06-07; Intercambios 06-07; LAC Regional: PPD 06-07; MVA Distribution 07; Martin contract 07; Multilingual Glossary 07; MRC Contract 07; Young Contract FY07; IFHHRO FY07; Planning 07; M+E pilot 07; June '07 Regional Mtg.; Women's Link Worldwide Contract 07; MA 07-08; Regional Consultants 07-08; Indicators Workshop SDP Data 07; Uruguay MA Mtg 08; UNFPA FY08; Rebecca Giguere Contract FY08; Comms Workshop 08; SRR & SV pubs + presentations 08; LAC Newsletter FY08; MA Conference 08; CEMICAMP Uruguay Conf 08; PAHO Req Stats 08; UNFPA FY 08-11; CLACAI mtg 09; Strategic Planning 2009; FY09 MGMT DOCS; FLASOG workshops 09-10; Desk retreat FY09; Risk Mgmt/Security 10; Sustainable Supply FY10 (Box 183)
- Asia Programs, 1985-2012; 23 boxes
  Ipas began its work in Asia in 1985 in Turkey with the supply of MVA instruments to the Ministry of Health, followed by trainings of medical providers to expand and improve menstrual regulations services. Shortly thereafter, Ipas supplied instruments and developed interventions to improve infection prevention in the Bangladesh menstrual regulation program. In Vietnam, Ipas was part of the Reproductive Health Project starting in 1994 with Pathfinder International and AVSC (now EngenderHealth), and Ipas Vietnam opened its own office in 2000. Vietnam programs focused on assisting the Ministry of Health in developing National Abortion Standards and Guidelines, and expanding access to comprehensive abortion care services, including safe, high quality second trimester abortion services. In India, Ipas played a strategic role in putting safe abortion on the national reproductive health agenda with a seminal conference on safe abortion in Agra in October 2000. With a major private grant, Ipas opened an office in New Delhi in 2001. After the law change in Nepal in 2002 to legalize abortion services, Ipas provided technical assistance in the development of policy guidelines, and planning and implementing the safe abortion program. Ipas's programs in Vietnam, India and Nepal expanded dramatically from 2000 - 2006. Ipas provided technical and training support to start comprehensive abortion care services in Cambodia in 2004 and began developing programmatic plans in Pakistan in 2006.
  Ipas's main strategy in Asia was to work in countries where abortion was legal to remove barriers to access and demonstrate models of quality comprehensive abortion care, including medication abortion primarily in India and Vietnam. Asian countries presented great potential for impact to improve women's lives through public sector programs and integration with other reproductive health initiatives.
  Don Weeden was Ipas's Regional Desk (Director) for Asia Programs starting in 1999, followed by Traci Baird in 2002, and Wendy Darby in 2005, Amin Islam in 2009, and Karen Olsea in 2011.
  - India Programs, 1988-2012
    - Background files, PSS 88-94, corresp 95-99, trip reports 98 & 99, TAC abortion proposal 99, PRIME India 99-01, donor proposals/reports/corres 00, trip reports 00, country team mtgs 00, P Bhiwandi speech MVA congress 00, pop policy 00, PRIME II ANE 00, Famycare 00, MVA in India background paper 00, Janani/Liam 00-02, donor reports/reports/corres 01, program highlights/country report 01, trip reports 01, Ipas India presentation 01, Agra early abortion meeting working files 01, FOGSI/Ipas presentation 01, research papers 01, DV vs SV instruments 01, instrument specs 01, abortion in India lit review 01, Prastut consulting lit review and marketing report 01, marketing associate 01, marketing 01, MOH MVA guidelines 01, MIS program numbers 01, Contech 01, Dai Ichi Karkaria 01, marketing trip 01, Parkash 01, Mercator 01, Sisco 01, team mtgs 01, communication 01, DFID/SIDA proposal/comms/report 01, strategic planning 01, office materials 01, position descriptions 01, office setup 01-02, JMS 01-02, TA for AAP proposal 01-03, Romsons 01-04, 1988-2004 (Box 96)
    - Donor proposals/reports/corres 02, planning 02, env scan 02, program presentations 02, marketing research and plan 02, Romsons MOU 02, Krishnan consultancy 02, FOGSI workshops 02, Shah consultancy 02, TOT/scale-up/counseling materials 02, monitoring 02, GOI 02, office lease 02, team mtgs 02, Orissa workshops 02, country report 02, FOGSI presentation 02, trip reports 02, Bihar/Jharkhand (BJ) project 02-04, Eurodonor proposal 02-05, donor proposals/reports/corres 03, safe abortion workshop Delhi 03, program overview 03, program report 03, office lease 03, Eurodonor and staffing needs 03, WHO mtg 03, program review 03, TOT materials 03, TOT reports 03, results numbers 03, Pop Council 03-04, MTP Act changes 03-04, DFID logframe 03, program planning 03, team orientation 03, SIDA proposal 03, policy analysis 03, WHO guidance launch contract 03, Maharashtra donor proposal/report 03-05, donor proposal/reports 04, FOGSI 04, planning 04,Reserve Bank of India 04, MTP and NPP comparative analysis 04, small grants 04, Society registration 04, marketing 04, AAP 04, consultants 04-06, Ipas India pubs 04-06, Ipas in India report 05, MVA distribution 05, KVGK subcontract 05, Safe Abortion Care donor proposals/report 05-06, Maharashtra proposal 05-07, project updates 05-06, sex selection abortion presentation 06, marketing 06, Maharashtra planning 06, CAC donor proposal 06-09, Bihar/Jharkhand donor proposal 06-08, 2002-2006 (Box 97)
    - W Bengal 00; PSS Rajastan proposal 00; MVA studies 00; Martin Pinto 01; background 02; FOGSI press coverage 02; Bela's presentations 02-03; trip reports 02-05; AB assessment project 03; office lease 03; Pop Council 03-05; Pop Health Srvc 03-08; office lease 04: FOGSI consensus statement 04; sex selection AB 04; BAIF subcontract 04; B/J SDA subcontract 04; India Friends Society 04-05; Pioneer Club launch 05; Anon6 report 05; local society MOU 04; FPAI subcontract 05-07; misc notes 05-09; Pop Council 06; MVA article 06; misc corresp 06; planning 06; B/J donor report 06; Consortium CAC proposal 06; office lease 06; SIDA 06-07; misc corresp 06-07; Ipas India mats 06-07; workplans/progress 06-07; PPD 06-08; local entity 06-08; Uttaranchal contact 06-09; Consortium extensions 06-09; CAC donor reports 06-09; SIDA consortium subgrantee agreements 07; DKT subcontract 07; summary Ipas projects 07; trip report 07; gen corresp 07; program planning mtg 07; GEM 07; CAC scale-up Maharashtra proposal 07; marketing donor proposal 07; MAPnet 07; MA pilot project 07; B/J outcomes agreement 07; staff activities 07; MAPnet MA network 07; MA Jharkand 07; mid-level providers 07; pubs 07; M&E 07; finance structure 07; misc corresp 07; trip reports 07; ARTH 07-08; country update 07—08; MA 07-09; FPA 07-09; FOGSI 07-09; CEHAT 07-09; ANS 07-09; Scaling up Maharashtra donor concept paper 07-10; MOUs 07-10, 1999-2007 (Box 159)
    - Making Abortions Safer Mtg 08; RFPs 08; gen corresp 08; trip reports 08; B/J proposa; 08; Pharma mkt analysis 08; job description 08; SIDA global 08; planning mtg 08; DISHA 08; misc contracts 08; M&E 08; FY 08 planning notebook; sex selection 08-09; contracts 08-09; presentations/studies 08-09; office registration 08-09; Ipas sites 08-09; program summary results 08-10; govt of Maharashtra 09-11; CINI 09; employee climate survey 09; PSI 09; student MVA report 09; MTP revision 09; FPAI MOU 09; corresp 09; planning 09; MGVS 09; MGVS #2 09; MGVS #3 09; env scan 09; planning 09; MA study 09; MSI 09; B/H donor report 09; donor mtg 09; CAC GOI guidelines 09; PPD 09; HR 09; community/Jharkand pres 09; trip report 09; results overview 09; contracts 09-10; CINI 09-10; LGSS 09-10; contact base 09-10; IDF 09-10; GVPS 09-10; trip reports 09-10; Pop Council sub-award 09-10; strat planning report 10; MP/Ipas CAC 10; GEM results 10; VCAT logistics 10; background 10; PSI project 10; Pop Council 10; Youth presentation 10; summary report 10; ARTH presentations 10; CAC donor reports 10; Center for Media Studies 10; comm skills training module 10; Jainani MOU 10; UP PAFP – FHI 10-11; B/J proposal 10-12, 2008-2010 (Box 160)
  - Nepal Programs, 1995-2010
    - FHI legal reform project 95-96, PAC services report 96, AGI Nepal article review 01, Options 01, background articles/reports 01-02, MOH terms of reference 02, Policy/lit review 02, Human rights/maternal mortality report 02, lessons learned presentation 02, trip reports 02, Making AB safe and legal mtg 02, policy work 02, law amendment 02, CREPHA/Ipas concept paper 02, chrono 02-03, safe motherhood 03, Options TOR 03, Options proposal 03, Options 03, Options report 03, FWLD 03, TCIC contract 03-04, planning and comms 03-04, articles/reports 03-04, Potter contract 03-04, CREHPA contracts 03-06, chrono 04, Options 04, Maternity hospital 04, MA assessment 04, CAC training manual 04, RHTRA contract 04-05, TCIC/RHTRA contracts 04-05, general 04-05, Thomas contracts 04-05, DFID/SSMP reports 04-05, CAC monitoring 04-06, chrono 05, historical summary 05, chrono 05, donor proposal tech advisor 05, CREHPA proposal 05, briefing 05, CAC reference manual 05, options proposal 05, FWLD small grants 05, trip reports 05-06, Options agreement 05-06, articles/reports 05-06, Bird 05-06, TCIC reports 05-06, TCIC plan 05-08, corresp 06, CAC monitoring map data 06, CAC training MOH 06, CAC provider mtgs 06, Ipas in Nepal presentation 06, Maternal mortality study 06, 1995-2006 (Box 98)
    - SSMP notebook 99-06; background 99-06; Safe Motherhood plan 02; Options Proposal/contract 02-04; Options proposal 03; pubs/press 03-07; background 04; articles/handouts/reports 04-10; MOH plans 04-15; timeline 05; Dr L Thomas trip reports 05; inventory list 05-07; MA workshop 05; TCIC mtg 05; MOH CAC manuals 05; Options DFID submission 05; SSMP planning mtg 05; Safer Motherhood 05; Pilot BCC report 05; presentations 05-08; Ipas summaries 05-08; TCIC perf management 06; TCIC IEC plan 06; indicators 06; M Goetsch 06-07; misc notes/reports 06-07; misc materials 06-07; corresp 06-09; C Bird contract 07; MVA 07; AB study findings 07; Options agreement 07; RH protocols 07; CAC Ab study 07; 2nd tri workshop 07; SSMP biannual report 07; corresp 07; trip reports 07; RHTRA 07; M&E pilot 07; Options audit 07; job vacancy 07; TCIC misc 07; board bullets 07-08; articles/reports 07-08; RHTRA and other contracts 07-08; workplans and budgets 07-09; Options invoices 07-09; country stats 07-09; trip reports 07-10, 1999-2007 (Box 165)
    - IEC 08; Anon2 global concept paper 08; Anon2 final reports 08; CAC complications study 08; CREPHA 08; Medabon 08; FIGO 08; TCIC advocacy strat 08; trainee F-U 08; non-Ipas trip report 08; CAC PHD subcontract 08; Options contract 08; Options SSMP audit 08; audit docs 08; TCIC/RHTRA agreements 08; RHTRA agreement 08; Kathmandu hospital study 08; RHTRA release ltrs 08; CAC HMIS tools 08; Maguire trip report 08; Ipas office 08; Options/TCIC budget 08-09; DFID SSPM reports 08-09; MA 08-09; planning 08; IEC mats 08-09; 2nd tri 08-09; subcontracts 09; RHTRA subcontract 09; office 09; PSI/Ipas agreement 09; results 09; JSI/Anon2 budget 09; Kusum Thapa 09; CAC comp study dissemination 09; MA recruitment 09; trip report 09; Gynuity mtg 09; DFID concept paper 09; Options subcontract 09; external audits 09; office plans/budget 09; RWD proposals 09; MA WHO Study 09; reports/pubs 09-10; PSI 09-10; consultant contracts 09-10; TSDI data 09-10; MOUs 09-10 NGO reg 09-10; CAC ads 26 languages 09; comp study 09-10; reports/presentations 09-10; program/results summary 10; subcontracts 10; WCG Sino implant 10; midwives 10; 2nd tri equipment 10; MA data 10; web story 10; M&E proposals 10; trip report 10; case study 10; individual workplans 10; finance notes 10; MA pilot model 10; presentations 10; MA scale-up 10; MVA site data 10; annual planning 10; improving results 10; background 10; MA pilot report 10; Options tech proposal 10; Anon2 proposal 10, 2008-2010 (Box 166)
  - Vietnam Programs, 1988-2010
    - Background 88-96, background 89-95, AVSC 89-99, corresp 90-97, FHI project 93, FHI AB study 93-95, FHI meetings 93-95, MOH comms 93-95, RHP development/proposals/reports 93-96, RHP trip reports 93-96, AVSC 93-96, Phamatech 93-96, trip reports non-Ipas 93-96, interagency mtg 94, Ipas background document 94, eval 94-96, Pathfinder comms 94-96, curriculum 94-95, RHP field reports 94-96, phamatech 94-96, Bourne corresp 94-96, RHP modules, RHPO MOU with MOH 95, Tyson 95-96, Ipas research 95-96, key memos 95-96, RHP misc reports 95-96, 1988-1996 (Box 99)
    - Site change plans 96, WHO assessment 96, RHP qtrly reports 96, Ipas country report 96, APHA panel 96, RHP mtg 96, RHP reports 96-97, M&E 96-97, comms 96-99, PACCOM 96-00, med records background 97, PHamatech 97, RHP working files 97, Hanh ICR 97, national standards workshop 97, RHIARC 97-98, trip reports non-Ipas 97-00, reach numbers 97-01, double valve study 98, donor reports 98, trip reports 98, country strategy 98, Hanh 98, field reports 98-99, 2nd trimester project 98-02, trip reports 99, educ mats 99, RHP report 99, donor reports 99, RHP qtrly reports 99-00, comms 99-00, team mtgs 99-00, RHP workplan 99-03, Ipas program overview 00, donor report 00, RHP MOU 00, RHP modules 00, RHP lessons learned 00, internal reports 00, World Bank 00, RHP strategic appraisal team 00-01, reports 00-01, trip reports 00, Quality of Care workshop report 00, RHP assessment reports 00-01, RHP reports 00-02, Ipas VN country team 00-01, RHP misc 00-03, 1996-2000 (Box 100)